To save his future he must alter his past.
Synchronicity is a mystery, science fiction,
thriller film directed by Jacob Gentry.
A daring physicist travels into the past to stop a
mysterious woman from stealing his invention.
But once there, he uncovers a surprising truth about the
machine, the woman, and his own fractured reality.
Jim Beale, played by Chad McKnight.
Abby, played by Brianne Davis.
Chuck, played by AJ Bowen.
Matty, played by Scott Poythress.
Klaus Meisner, played by Michael Ironside.
Helen Meisner, played by Claire Bronson.
Synchronicity is a 2015 American science fiction film
written, directed, and edited by Jacob Gentry.
It stars Chad McKnight, A.
Bowen, Brianne Davis, Scott Poythress, and Michael Ironside.
McKnight plays a physicist who invents a time machine and becomes
suspicious that others may be trying to steal the technology.
It premiered at the 2015 Fantasia International Film Festival and had a limited
release in theaters and on video on demand and iTunes on January 22, 2016.
The film explores themes of time travel, wormhole, time
machine, confusion, beautiful woman.
The tone is intense and dark and thought_provoking.